

267-475-0725

tanubiz19@gmail.com

www.tanuseth.com

in www.linkedin.com/in/tanuseth9

Cleveland 44136, United States



## **PROJECTS**

Created during my CareerFoundry UX/UI Certification Course

2020 -2021

#### PAYLIGHT - VIRTUAL WALLET MOBILE WEB APP

UX Researcher and Designer

As a sole UX designer, I designed this project from inception to final visual design through research, ideation and UX design principles including wireframing and prototyping in Figma.

2021

#### PERFECT HOME - REAL ESTATE RESPONSIVE WEB APP

UX/UI Designer

As a sole UX/UI designer, I designed this app in Figma by applying UX and Visual Design fundamentals and methodologies.

2021

#### LANGOON - LANGUAGE LEARNING MOBILE WEB APP

UX Researcher and Designer

I designed this project in Adobe XD from start to finish through design thinking process which includes research and development of strategic design solutions, usability testing and hand-off documentation.



## **EDUCATION**

2020 - 2021

#### CERTIFICATE IN UX/UI DESIGN

CareerFoundry - Germany (Remote)

Specialized in intensive UX focused curriculum along with three hands-on projects. Additional specializations include coursework in UI and front-end development. The course included UX design thinking process and methodology, such as user research, user personas, wireframing, prototyping, usability testing, information architecture, and visual design.

2017-2018

## CERTIFICATE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

Renton Technical College - United States

Learned programing basic fundamentals such as C# (.net), Python(PyCharm), UX & Web-Designing, Networking, QA/Software Testing, PC Hardware and Networking, Microsoft Office Applications, and Business Communication.

1998-2002

## **BACHELOR OF COMMERCE**

Delhi University - India

Commerce, Accounting, Math, Economics, Hindi, English



# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

2019-2020

## **ASSISTANT TEACHER**

All Around Children - United States

Managed classroom of up to 25 students, created weekly lesson plans and daily activities for children, engaged children in interactive activities that includes storytelling, organizing art and crafts, and Instructed children in circle time while teaching Math, English, and other subjects.

2007-2011

## **ADMISSION EXECUTIVE**

Sir Ganga Ram Hospital - India

Scheduled doctor appointments, conducted check-ins/check-outs of patients, assisted individuals with disabilities, processed billing, payments, and insurance. Coordinated with doctors to get their rosters in the system.

2004-2007

## **ADMINISTRATIVE ASSISTANT**

Sri Balaji Action Medical Institute - India

Made patient admissions and discharges, handled billing and payments, managed doctor appointments, insurance submissions, approvals, and public dealings.

# I believe that there is always room for improvement.

# **PROFILE**

I am a UX Designer with an educational background in computer science and technology focused on creating experiences that are meaningful and valuable for a customer with a mobile first approach in mind. I aim for the entire user experience to be inclusive, appealing and user centered. I involve users throughout the design process via a variety of research and design techniques to create highly usable and accessible products.

#### Tools

FIGMA

ADOBE XD

AXURE

**PHOTOSHOP** 

**GIMP** 

**USABILITY HUB** 

OPTIMAL WORKSHOP

GOOGLE FORMS

HTML

CSS

JAVASCRIPT

MS OFFICE

# **UX Skills**

PROBLEM SOLVING

RESEARCH

DESIGN THINKING

COMPETITIVE ANALYSIS

BUSINESS REQUIREMENTS

USER INTERVIEWS

SURVEYS

USER PERSONAS | STORIES

CARD SORTING | AFFINITY MAPPING

WIREFRAMING

PROTOTYPING

**USABILITY TESTING** 

PREFERENCE AND A/B TESTING

USER FLOWS

INFORMATION ARCHITECTURE

STYLE GUIDES

VISUAL DESIGN

DESIGN SYSTEM AND DOCUMENTATION

HIGH FIDELITY MOCKUPS

# Interpersonal Skills

COMMUNICATION
TEAMWORK
PRESENTATION
CREATIVITY

ANALYTICAL THINKING